UNITE Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board Research Files 6000/021
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board Research Files
1983- 2002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board
6000/021
13 cubic feet
13 linear ft.
Records.
5751539
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
D Cohen, February 17, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs 6000/016: UNITE Local 169 Files 6000/016 MB: UNITE Local 169 Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board Memorabilia Banners 6000/016 P: UNITE Local 169 Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board Photographs
Clothing workers, Labor unions, New York (State); Food service employees, Labor unions, New York (State); Health facilities, Employees, Labor unions, New York (State); Textile workers, Labor unions, New York (State); ABC Health Service Registry, Archives; BMP America, Inc., Archives; Crysteel Manufacturing, Inc., Archives; Express Navigation, Archives; Fulton County Census of Business, Archives; Lulu's Cafe, Archives; Monroe County (N.Y.) Visiting Nurses Association, Archives; Nationwide Precision Products Corporation, Archives; Party Rental Limited, Archives; Rochester (N.Y.) Visiting Nurses Association, Archives; SPX Corporation, Archives; Syracuse Gauge, Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees, Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board, Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization), Archives; Yale CO-OP, Archives
5751539
- ABC Health Service Registry, 1984-2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Albany Cab Companies, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Alleson of Rochester Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Arcom, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Arrow Shirt-Chile, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- BMP America Inc., 1995-2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bicycle Messengers, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Boys Club of New York, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Brighton Beach Grocers, New York State Labor Board, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Broadway Deli, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- CAAV Committee Against Asian American Violence, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- C&N Fruit, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cantisano Foods Inc., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Capehorn Industries, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Cardinal Healthcare Inc., 1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Champion rock Products Inc., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Cineplex Odeon Worldwide Theater (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Chick Chack Inc., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Cittero (Euro Foods Inc.), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Citimarkets LLC, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- CMT Knitwear Inc., 1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Columbia Omni Corp., 2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Coliseum Books Inc., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Cookson Group / Cookson PLC, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- cookson Group PLC General Information, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Cookson PLC Annual Report, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Cookson Group PLC (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Cookson PLC Annual Report, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Coyne Laundry, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Crysteel Manufacturing Inc., 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Curtin Herbert Co., 1998 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Culinart Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Cycle Couriers Inc., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Cygne Designs Inc., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- DBL Couriers Inc., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Eagle Comtronics Inc., 1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Early Bird Express Delivery Inc., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- East Natural Greenwich Village Market, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Eileen Fisher, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Euromed Inc. (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Erdle Perforation Co. Inc., 1999 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Express Navigation, 1991-1999 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Federal Business Products/Federal Direct, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Fibertek Energy LLC, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Fifth Ave Committee, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Fine Fare, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- First Ave Fruit and Vegetables, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Garden of Eden, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Greene Uniform co., 1999 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- H&E Machinery Inc., 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- H&S Fruit and Vegetable Market, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Healthy Pleasures, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Higbee Gasket & Sealing Products Inc., 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Homes, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Immigration, 1991-2000 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- International Car Wash Association, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Internet, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Jakes Home Deliveries, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Jo Jo Sportswear Inc., 1999 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Johnstown Knitting Mills, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Jump Apparel Co., 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Kim's video IV Inc., 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Lexington Industries/Fulton County Arc, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Lexington Precision Corp., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Lime Market Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Little Lady Sportswear Inc., 1998 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Looper Inc., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- LTX Fibre LLC, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Lucky Farms, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- LuLu's Caf, 1987-2001 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- M & K Eighty-Eight Cleaners, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Mc Clean Service, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Magnus Manufacturing Corp., 1999 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Marietta Corp., 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Maxene Cleaners And Tailors, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- MaClean Northeast Corp., 2001 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Marpac Industries Inc., 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- McKenchnie Plastic Packaging, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Messenger Services, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- MBJ Cafeteria Vending Corp., 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Metropolitan Food Service, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Minimum/Living Wage, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Minnesota Mining & Manufacturing Co. Inc., 1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- William B. Morse Lumber Co., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Muri Lu Knitting Mill Inc., 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Mustang Sportswear, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- The New Press/Fund for Independent Publishing, 1992-2001 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Nationwide Precision Products Corp., 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Native Textile, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Nelson Air Device Corp., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- New Alliance - AFL-CIO Restructuring, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- New Dong International, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- New Energy Works of Rochester Inc., 1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- New Times Market Inc., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- New York Psychiatric Institute, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- New York Retail, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- New York Tissue, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- PQ Linen Services, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Pacamor Kubar Bearings, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Pan De Casa Inc., 1998 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Party Rental Limited, 1985-2000 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Penthouse Industries Inc., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- People Inc., 1999 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Performance Fabrications Inc., 1999 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Personal Touch Valet Plant Inc., 2001 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Pergola, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Plaza Packaging Corp., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Proprecision Bicycle Works, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Prepaid Legal Services Inc., 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Prestige First Ave Cleaning Corp., 2001 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Rotondo Trucking and Warehouse Inc., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Queensboro Cleaners Inc., 2001 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Sample Contracts, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Schoolhouse Warehouse Inc., 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- 7th St. Food, Vegetable and grocery, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- 75 Park, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Simply Everything, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- SPX Corp. 1/2, 1994-2001 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- SPX Corp. 2/2, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Specialized Packaging International, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Staub Textile Services Inc., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Stevins Apparel Inc., 1999 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Stingy Lulu's (Box 2, Folder 47)
- B.G. Sulzle inc., 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Sweatshops - New York City Daily Newsseries, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Syracuse Banana Co. Inc., 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Syracuse Gauge, 1983-1999 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Sysco Corporation, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- 3 Backstage Eatery Corp., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- 240 Merit Corp., 2001 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Taconic Direct Mail Inc., 1998 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- top - Lowereast Side Market, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Upper Yorkville Cleaners Inc., 2001 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Charges Against Two Brothers, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Turner Bellows Inc., 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Tyco International Inc., 2001 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Ultrafab Inc., 1999 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Upstate Disposal Inc. (Subs. Republic Services), 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- United Dominion Industries Inc., 1999 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Ventre Packing Co. Inc., 1999 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Visiting Nurses Assn. of Rochester and Monroe County, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Volunteers of America, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Wackenhut Corp., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Walmart Corp., 1998 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Warm Front, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- We Care Transportation Inc., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Westplex Industries Corp., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- West Side Market, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- White Sun Cleaners Corp., 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Yale Co-op, 1993-1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Zero Insertion Force Inc., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Organizing - General, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Organizing Legal Issues, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Nothereast Regional Joint Board, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board Newsletters, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Article XX, 1989-1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Blind Materials, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Coda (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Computer Information (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Discrimination, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Health and Safety Leaflets, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Oneida County, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Gallagher Articles/Staughton Lynd, 1994-1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- BNA Publications and Info, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- 401(k) Info, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Sol-Lain Park Committee, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- United Hebrew Trades, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Labor Religion Coalition, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Fulton County Census of Business, 1990-1996 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- BMP America Inc., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Union Summer, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- NLRB ULP Info - English & Spanish, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Website Info, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- delegate Information (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Union Corruption, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Workplace Project, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Baggage Transfer Companies, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Cafeterias, 1987-1998 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Industrial Development Agencies, 1992-1998 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Labor Day Parade, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Flag Pole and Banner Info, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Taxi Drivers, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Permits - Parks, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Textiles, 1988-1998 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Temporary Employees, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Stock Leaflets (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Wild Oaks Markets Inc. (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Pearl Paint - Newsletter (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Contract Notes & Materials (Box 4, Folder 2)
- final Proposals with Notes (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Proposals (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Information Request (Box 4, Folder 5)
- central Art Supply Local 810 IBT Contract & Notes (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Contract Campaign - Artist Groups (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Worker Lists (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Plans & Notes (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Targets - Overview (Box 4, Folder 10)
- H & S Issues (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Denihan (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Flex-o-Tex Drapery Cleaners Inc. (Box 4, Folder 13)
- M & K Eighty Eight Cleaners Inc. (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Maxene Cleaners and Tailors (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Personal Touch Valet (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Prestige First Ave Cleaning Corp. (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Queensboro Cleaners Inc. (Box 4, Folder 18)
- White Sun Cleaners Corp. (Box 4, Folder 19)
- 240 Merit Corp. (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Upper Yorkville Cleaners Inc. (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Targets - Unicore SIC 7389 Misc. Business Services (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Organizing Targets Targets, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Scope and Contents
  January 7
- Cibao Meat Producing (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Korean Produce Association Sweatshops (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Organizing (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Roto Rooter (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Jack's (Box 4, Folder 28)
- ULP 8a1-2 (UFCW Local 348-s) (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Jewelry - SIC's (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Jewelry - Industry (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Jewelry Manufacturing (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Jewelry Locations (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Jewelry - Unions/Workers (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Probe Schedule and Reports (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Andel Jewelry and Other Queens Shops (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Alarama / Aha Casting / Overnight Mountings 2121 44 Dr. LIC NY 1101 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Jewelry - Riva (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Tiffany's Sourcing (Box 4, Folder 39)
- United Brothers Jewelry (Box 4, Folder 40)
- W. W. Jewelry Inc. (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Jewelry MSO (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Reference List (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Survey (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Jewelry Queens (Box 4, Folder 45)
- UNITE 2001 Laundry Conference - San Francisco, Oct. 4-5, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- UNITE 2001 Laundry Conference: Folder 2 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Queens Manufacturing List, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  February
- Food Processing Bklyn/Queens (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Queens Distribution Centers (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Greengrocers Misc. (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Nushwick Target List (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Queens Target Lists as of July 15, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Brookyn Targets List (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Retail (Box 4, Folder 55)
- NLRB Elections, 1990-2000 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  Rochester Area
- NLRB Elections, 1990-2000 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  Syracuse Area
- NLRB Elections, 1990-2000 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  Albany Area
- NLRB Petitions Field, 1990-2000 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- NLRB Petitions Field, 1990-2000 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- NLRB Petitions Field, 1990-2000 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  Buffalo/Rochester
- NLRB Elections, 1990-2000 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  Region 3
- NLRB Statistical Data (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Solutions to Problems (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 22 Textiles (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 23 Apparel (Box 4, Folder 66)
- SIC 2515 Mattresses and Bed Springs (Box 4, Folder 67)
- SIC 28, 29 Adhesives, Sealents, and Resins (Box 4, Folder 68)
- SIC 30 Rubber Goods, Extruded and Injected Molded Plastic Goods (Box 4, Folder 69)
- SIC 3842 Surgical Appliance and Supplies (Box 4, Folder 70)
- SIC 4212 Local Trucking w/out storage (Box 4, Folder 71)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 4212 Local Trucking Without Storage (Box 4, Folder 72)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 5092 Toys, Hobby Goods and Supplies (Box 4, Folder 73)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 56 Retail Stores, Warehousing Retail (Box 4, Folder 74)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 72 Laundry and Dry Cleaning Establishments (Box 4, Folder 75)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 7389 Miscellaneous Business Services (Box 4, Folder 76)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 22 Textiles (Box 4, Folder 77)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 23 Apparel (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 2515 Mattresses and Bed Springs (Box 4, Folder 79)
- Syracuse Area Targets SICs 28 and 29 Adhesives, Sealents, and Resins (Box 4, Folder 80)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 30 Rubber Goods, Extruded and Injected Molded Plastics (Box 4, Folder 81)
- Syracuse/Utica Area Machine Shop SIC 3559.3562.3569 (Box 4, Folder 82)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 3842 Surgical Appliance and Supplies (Box 4, Folder 83)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 4212 Local Trucking Without Storage (Box 4, Folder 84)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 5092 Toys, Hobby Goods and Supplies (Box 4, Folder 85)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 56 Retail Stores, Warehousing Retail (Box 4, Folder 86)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 72 Laundry and Dry Cleaning Establishments (Box 4, Folder 87)
- Syracuse Area Targets SIC 7389 Miscellaneous Business Services (Box 4, Folder 88)
- Target - Brooklyn - Bushwick (Box 4, Folder 89)
- Long Island Targets (Box 4, Folder 90)
- Retail - New York City (Box 4, Folder 91)
- Brooklyn - NLRB Elections, 1983-1999 (Box 4, Folder 92)
- Fraiche Negotiations (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Fraiche - Reco (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Two Brothers (Box 5, Folder 3)
- East Natural, Abbigail, SOHO (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Eldre Corp. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Hee I & II (Box 5, Folder 6)
- H & S NLRB (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Hee II Service (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Graceland Farm Contracts (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Graceland Farms 24 Ave A NY, NY (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Graceland (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Fuji (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Fuji Apple - NLRB (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Divine Brothers Strike (Box 5, Folder 14)
- BMP America Inc. (Box 5, Folder 15)
- BG Sulzle Inc. (Box 5, Folder 16)
- 118 1st Ave FLV - NLRB - Petition (Box 5, Folder 17)
- 118 1st Ave F&U ULP Union (Box 5, Folder 18)
- 118 1st Ave Fruit and Vegetables (NLRB) Corp. (Box 5, Folder 19)
- 118 1st Ave Recognition (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Greengrocery 118 1st Ave (Box 5, Folder 21)
- 118 1st Ave F & V Corp. (Box 5, Folder 22)
- NLRB Petition 1st Ave Gourmet (Box 5, Folder 23)
- 1st Ave Gourmet Deli - ULP (Box 5, Folder 24)
- 1st Ave Gourmet Deli 196 1st Ave NY, NY 10009 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Valentino Misc. Negotiations Notes & Wage Calculations (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Sonny & Annie NLRB Election Petition (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Sonny & Annie Card Check Agreement / Recognition (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Sunny & Annie Gourmet Deli 94 Ave B Ny,NY 10003 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Mi Sook Lee's Market (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Arc (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Ames Linen Service (Box 5, Folder 32)
- All State Stamping - Syracuse (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Agrilink - Brockport (Box 5, Folder 34)
- LM-10 Filings (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Albany County Laundries (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Fraiche 213 Park Ave NLRB - Petition (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Fraiche II - Affidavits Duplicates (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Fraiche II Affidavits (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Fraiche (6 E. 48th St.) (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Fraiche Assault Case of Manuel Guerrero (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Fraiche 213 Park Ave. S NY, NY 10008 460-0910 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Fraiche 213 Park Ave ULP (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Targets (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Ownership Information (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Valentino Petition NLRB (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Valentino Card Check Agreement (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Valentino Recognition (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Valentino (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Mr. Fulton - Youn's Coffee Shop (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Fulton Grill - Fulton Corp. (Box 5, Folder 51)
- NLRB ULP Adinah's Farm (Box 5, Folder 52)
- NLRB - Employer Charge (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Leaflets (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Adinah's Farms - Employer's Leaflets - Yellow Dog Contract (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Strikers - Sign in Ray Records (Box 5, Folder 56)
- NLRB - Election (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Press Conference (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Supporters (Box 5, Folder 59)
- US Dept of Labor (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Adinah's Farms (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Open Letter (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Press (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Adinah's Farms DOL (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Adinah's Farms - Servicing (Box 5, Folder 65)
- NLRB Election (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Notes / Meeting / Chronology (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Committee (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Company Policies (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Plates (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Research (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Crysteel D & B Current (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Economic Packages (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Customers (Box 6, Folder 9)
- UNITE Companies & Contract (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Crysteel (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Company Handbook / Guidelines (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Card Signing (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Teamster Letter (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Crysteel Company Lit. (Box 6, Folder 15)
- UNITE Lit. (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Crysteel Inc. (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Plans (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Budget (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Schedules/Misc. (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Jan 2 Shop DU (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Supporters - I - S, RWDSU (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Org Comm (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Jan 6/7 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Ratings Jan 4 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Zip Code 1/4, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Card Rating 1/3, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Alpha List 1/2 Excelsior, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Dept - Loc - Name List 1/2, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Worker Lists 12/24 - 12/29 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Worker Lists (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Worker Lists 9/30, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Targets (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Contact With Signals (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Union Lit (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Jack's Photos (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Company Lit. (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Petition (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Cards (Box 6, Folder 39)
- ULPs (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Store Info (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Personnel Manual (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Korean Recognition (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Contracts / Recognition Agreements (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Reco Letters - 2001 For Green Grocery Campaign English and Korean (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Green grocery Campaign List of Documents Sent to Cornell (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Card Checking Agreement (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Generic Contracts Greengrocers (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Contracts - In Korean (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Nu Way (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Northern Health Care Linen Service Inc. (subs. Atlas Health Care Linen Services) (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Northern Country Shops (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Nationwide Precision Products Corp (Box 6, Folder 53)
- McLane/Eastern Inc. (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Machine Shops (Upstate NY) (Box 6, Folder 55)
- LTX Fibre LLC (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Lexington Precision Corp. (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Innovations Blow Molding Corp. (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Pearl Paint (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Cibao- Back Wages, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Contains bundles of envelopes
- Cibao- Back Wages, 1999-2001 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Cibao- Lawsuit against EJ, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Newspaper and Payroll Receipt, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  New York Times, October 1 and Payroll receipt for March 11-17
- Cibao- ULP- From Company- Re: Med Ins, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  10/17/01
- Tony, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Agrilink 2nd Shift, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Agrilink- 1st Shift, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Agrilink Info (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Agrilink- Profile, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Staff Benefits, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Consolidated UhP, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Brooklyn Groceries- Delis, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Cibao Contract Campaign, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Spanish and English
- Cibao Celebration, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- ULP, For Lawsuit Filed against EJ, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Election, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Eden Farm, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  English and Spanish
- Card Check Agreements- Korean translation (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Korean
- Korean Translations- Letters to Stores (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Dues, Initiations, Health Plan- Memo, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Undocumented Workers- Labor Disputes Contracts, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  12/16/99
- Korean Translations- (Community Labor Coalition), 2000 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  6/7/00, English and Korean
- Storeowners' Letters- Korean Translation, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  April; Small Stores; English and Korean
- Greengocery Lit. Packet, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  English, Korean, Spanish
- Stallion (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Staub Textile Services Inc., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  12/31/98